A Guide to the Frank H. Field papers, Rockefeller University Faculty FA160
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Manuscripts, 1966-1980; 2; 5.28 Cubic Feet
  - CIMS. i-Butane Reactant Gas Modified by... D.V. Bowen and F.H. Field, 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - CIMS. Ion Molecule Reactions, F.H. Field, 1969-1972 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - CIMS. Ion Molecule Reactions, F.H. Field, 1969-1972 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - CIMS. Mass Spectra of Different Compound Types, F.H. Field, 1970-1971 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - CIMS. XIX. n-Hexane and n-Octane... Tung Yang Yu and F.H. Field, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - CIMS. XX. Energy Effects and... M. Meot-Ner and F.H. Field, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - CIMS. III. Paraffin Hydrocarbons, M.S.B. Munson, F.H. Field, D.A. Becker, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - CIMS. XV. Polytertiary Alkylamines, T.A. Whitney, L.P. Klemann. F.H. Field, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - CIMS. VII. Reactions of. Benzene Ions Benzene, F.H. Field, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - CIMS. XIII. Reactions of Methylthiomethyl Acetate and... F.H. Field and D.P. Weeks, 1969-1970 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - CIMS. XI. Reachions of Methoxymethyl Formate and... D.P. Weeks and F.H. Field, 1968-1969 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Chemical Ionization Mass Spectrometry (CIMS). XXI, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    Scope and Contents note
    Reactions-t-C5-H11... S.G. Lias and F.H. Field.
  - CIMS. XXI. Reactions-t-C5-H11... S.G. Lias and F.H. Field, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - CIMS. XXI. Reactions-t-C5-H11... S.G. Lias and F.H. Field, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - CIMS. IX. Temperature and Pressure Studies with... F.H. Field, 1968-1969 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - CIMS. XVI. Temperature Effects in Tertiary Alkyl, W.A. Laurie and F.H. Field, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - CIMS XIV. Temperature Studies of Substituted... D.P. Weeks and F.H. Field, 1970-1973 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Chemical Ionization Mass Spectrometry (CIMS). X. Temperature Studies with Substituted... F.H. Field, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Chemical Ionization Mass Spectrometry (CIMS) of Complex Molecules. III... H. Ziffer, H.M. Fales, G. Milne, F.H. Field, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - CIMS of L-Methionine and L-Methionine Analogs, A. Cooper, O. Griffith, A. Meister, F.H. Field, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - CIMS of Quarternary Amines, J. Shabanowitz, P. Brynes, A. Maelicke, D.V. Bowen, F.H. Field, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Chemical Mass Markers in CIMS, D.V. Bowen and F.H. Field, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - CIMS at the Humble Oil and Refining Co., F.H. Field, undated (Box 9)
  - C-Methylation in Peptide Sequencing by... M. Mudgett, D.V. Bowen, T. Kindt, F.H. Field, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - A Comparative Study of Cytokinesins... H.N. Wood, M.E. Rennekamp, D.V. Bowen. F.H. Field. A.C. Braun, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Decomposition Rates of Excited Reaction... M. Meot-Ner and F.H. Field, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Detection System for Negative Ions in Mass Spect. A.L.C. Smit, M.A.J. Rossetto and F.H. Field, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Dimethyl Disulfide: An Attractant in... R.J. O'Connell, A.G. Singer, W.C. Agosta, C. Pfaffmann, D.V. Bowen, F.H. Field, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Drug Interactions with Methadone, M.J. Kreek, C.L. Gutjahr, J.W. Garfield, D.V. Bowen, F.H. Field, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - The Effect of Temperature on the Mass Specta of... F.H. Field, P. Hamlet,. W.F. Libby, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Effects of Liver Disease on Urinary Excretion of... F.H. Kreek, F.A. Bencsath, F.H. Field, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Fecal Excretion of Methadone and Its Metabolites... M.J. Kreek, C.L. Gutjahr, D.V. Bowen, F.H. Field, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Fecan Excretion of Methadone and Its Metabolites... D.V. Bowen, A.L.C. Smit, M.J. Kreek, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Gaseous Anion Chemistry, J.R. Lloyd, W.C. Agosta. F.H. Field, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Gaseous Anion Chemistry, J.R. Lloyd, W.C. Agosta, F.H. Field, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Gaseous Anion Chemistry, J.R. Lloyd, W.C. Agosta, F.H. Field, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Gaseous Anion Chemistry, Formation and Reactions of... A.L.C. Smit and F.H. Field, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Gaseous Anion Chemistry, Formation and Reactions of... A.L.C. Smit and F.H. Field, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Gaseous Anion Chemistry, Formation and Reactions of... A.L.C. Smit and F.H. Field, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Gaseous Anion Chemistry, Negative Chemical Ionization... J.R. Lloyd, F.H. Field, W.C. Agosta, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - H-D Exchange in Gaseous Anions, F.H. Field, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - H-D Exchange in Gaseous Anions, F.H. Field, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - A High-Performance Digital Timing System, R.F. Bonner, D.V. Bowen, A. Lipton, W. Sippach, F.H. Field, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - A High-Performance Digital Timing System, R.F. Bonner, D.V. Bowen, A. Lipton, W. Sippach, F.H. Field, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Ion-Molecule Reactions in Ethane, S.L. Bennett, S.G. Liasa, F.H. Field, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Isobutane Chemical Ionization Mass... D.V. Bowen, F.H. Field (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Isobutane CIMS of Urethane... G. Barany, A.L.C. Smit, D.V. Bowen, R.B. Merrifield, F.H. Field, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Isotype Exchange Reaction of OH or OD with... M. Meot-Ner, J.R. Lloyd, E.P. Hunter, W.A. Agosta, F.H. Field, 1979-1980 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Kinetics, Equilibrium and Negative Temperature... J.J. Soloman, M. Meot-Ner, F.H. Field, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Kinetics and Thermodynamics of Assoc. Reactions... M. Meot-Ner and F.H. Field, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Loss of Water from Ketones in... W.A. Agosta, D.V. Bowen, L. Brodsky, M.E. Rennekamp and F.H. Field, 1974-1975 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - The Mass Spectral Characterization of... G. Barany, D.V. Bowen, R.B. Merrifield, F.H. Field, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Methadone Metabolism, (multiple manuscripts), 1978-1980 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - N-Substituted Dopamine and 2-Amino-6... J. Ginos, J. Stevens, A. Dhar, 1979-1980 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - OH-Negative Chemical Ionization Mass Spectra of Steroids, T.A. Roy and F.H. Field, 1977-1978 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - OH-Negative Chemical Ionization Mass Spectra of Steroids, T.A. Roy and F.H. Field, 1977-1978 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - OH-Negative CIMS. Reactions of [OH] - with... A.L.C. Smit and F.H. Field, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Peptide Sequence Determination by Mass Spect., D.V. Bowen, P. Leclercq, H.R. Morris, P. Roepstorff, 1971-1975 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Peptide Sequencing by CIMS, M. Mudgett, J.A. Sogu, D.V. Bowen, F.H. Field, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Peptide Sequencing: The Utility of... D.V. Bowen, T.J. Kindt, M. Mudgett, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - The Presence of Circulating Plasticizers in... N.P.H. Ching, C.S. Subbaroyan, D.V. Bowen, A.L.C. Smit, C.E. Grossi, R.G. Hicks, F.H. Field, T.F. Nealon, Jr., 1976 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Reversible Reactions of Gaseous Ions (RRGI). I-III, D.P. Beggs and F.H. Field, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - RRGI. l-III., D.P. Beggs and F.H. Field, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - RRGI. IX. The Determination of the Stability... J.J. Solomon and F.H. Field, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Reversible Reactions of Gaseous Ions (RRGI). V. Electrostatic Interactions Calculations, F.H. Field, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - RRGI. V. Electrostatic Interactions Calculations, F.H. Field, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - RRGI. IV. Further Studies on the Equilibrium... S.L. Bennett and F.H. Field, 1971-1972 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - RRGI. VII. The Hydrogen System S050, S.L. Bennett and F.H. Field, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - RRGI X. The Intrinsic Stability of the Norbornyl Caton, J.J. Solomon and F.H. Field, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - RRGI. V. The Methane... S.L. Bennett and F.H. Field, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - RRGI. XVII. Methane... M. Munson and F.H. Field, 1967-1969 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - RRGI. VI. The NH3... S.L. Bennett and F.H. Field, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - RRGI. III. Studies with Methane at P... F.H. Field and D.P. Beggs, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - RRGI. VIII. The t-C4-H9+... J.J. Solomon and F.H. Field, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - The Source of Circulating Plasticizers in... N. Ching, C. Subbarayan, D.V. Bowen, A.L.C. Smit, C. Grossi. F.H. Field, T.F. Nealon, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Stability, Association and Dissociation in the... M. Meot-Ner and F.H. Field, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - The Stability of Some C7 Tertiary Alkyl... M. Meot-Ner, J.J. Solomon and F.H. Field, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Steriospecific Loss of Water from Bicyalic Ketones... W.A. Agosta, D.V. Bowen, L. Brodsky, M. Rennekamp and F.H. Field (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Temperature Dependence of the Reaction CO+... M. Meot-Ner, J.J. Solomon, F.H. Field, H. Gershinowitz, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - The Temperature Dependence of Some Cosmochemically... M. Meot-Ner and F.H. Field, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - The Temperature Dependence of Some Cosmochemically... M. Meot-Ner and F.H. Field, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Thermodynamic Ionization Energies and Charge... M. Meot-Ner and F.H. Field, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Thermal Transitions between Collisionally and... M. Meot-Ner and F.H. Field, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - The Toxic Effects of Plasticizers Found in... N. Ching, C. Subbarayon, C. Grossi, D.V. Bowen, A.L.C. Smit, F.H. Field, T.F. Nealon, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Unimolecular Thermal Decomposition Reactions of... M. Meot-Ner and F.H. Field, 1975-1976 (Box 15, Folder 13)
- Correspondence, 1952-1964; 3; 0.88 Cubic Feet
  - Correspondence Ac-Au (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Academic Press Inc., 1955-1957
    - Adamson, Arthur W., 1952
    - Ahrendt, M.E., 1962
    - American Institute of Physics, 1952
    - Anderson, J.A., Jr., 1954
    - Anderson, Robbin C., 1953
    - Applied Physics Corporation, 1957
    - Applied Research Laboratories, 1953
    - Atkins, Marc, 1964
    - Ausloos, Peter, 1962 1964
  - Correspondence Ba-Be (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Baeder, D.L., 1962 1964
    - Balaban, Al, 1958
    - Baldock, Russell, 1958
    - Barnes, Earle B., 1958
    - Barton, Henry A., 1956
    - Baschkin, B.B., 1962
    - Bauer, S.H., 1961
    - Beckey, H.D., 1963-1964
    - Bendix Aviation Corp., 1955
    - Beynon, J.H., 1961 1964
  - Correspondence Bi-Bu (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Bicknell, Robert, 1960
    - Boeder, D., 1964
    - Boren, Hoolis G., 1960
    - Boudart, M., 1960
    - Brandt, Preston L., 1958
    - Brown, A.E., 1964
    - Brown, W.J., 1953
    - Buchta, J.W., 1956
    - Burnaby, Wilbur, 1963-1964
    - Burton, Milton, 1963
  - Correspondence Ca-Cu (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Cadle, Richard D., 1960
    - Calcotte, H.F., 1963
    - Cameron, Thomas B., 1952
    - Carlson, T.A., 1962
    - Carman, Max F., Jr., 1962
    - Caves, Tom, undated
    - Ceskoslovenska Akademie, 1959
    - Chalmers, J., 1954
    - Cloyd, W. P, 1953
    - Collin, Jacques E., 1963
    - Cook, C.J., 1963
    - Cramer, W.H., 1960
    - Currie, Amy S., 1964
    - Curtiss-Wright Corp., 1957
    - Cuthbert, J., 1963
  - Correspondence Da-Di (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Dahler, John S., 1961
    - Dainton, Fred, 1964
    - Dauben, Hyp J., Jr., 1957
    - Davis, Clyde L., 1954
    - Davis, Jeff C., Jr., 1960
    - Detrick, S.R., 1952
    - Dibeler, Vernon, 1952 1955-1961
  - Correspondence Do-Du (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Dockendorff, R.L., 1959
    - Doering, William, 1957-1958
    - D'Or, L., 1963
    - Dorfman, Leon M., 1960 1962
    - Draeger, A.A., 1954-1957 1959
    - Draper, L., 1962
    - Drowart, J., 1962
    - Duncan, A.B.F., 1963
  - Correspondence Ea-Ev (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Eager, R.L., 1964
    - Ebsworth, E.A.V., 1963
    - Edwards, D.V., 1956-1957
    - Elliott, R.M., 1962
    - Emanuel, W.L., 1953 1956 1962
    - Evans, Hugh E., 1962 1964
  - Correspondence Fa-Fo (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Fansteel Metallurgical Corp., 1955
    - Faraday Society, 1964
    - Ferguson, H.W., 1955
    - Filbert, Bryson M., 1952
    - Fincke, M.F., 1958
    - Fineman, Morton A., 1962
    - Forster, E.D., 1962
    - Fox, Russell E., 1958 1961-1962
  - Correspondence Franklin, Joseph E. (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Franklin, Joseph E., 1953-1958 1960-1964
  - Correspondence Fra-Fu (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Franklin, W.B., 1952
    - Freiser, Henry, 1959-1960
    - Friedel, R.A., 1958
    - Frost, David, 1960
    - Futrell, Jean HY, 1960 1964
  - Correspondence Ga-Gr (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Gates, Marshall D., Jr., 1963
    - Gatlin, Harold, 1952-1953
    - Geballe, Ronald, 1959
    - Geraghty, Frank, 1956
    - Gieger, Geraldine, 1955
    - Gille, K.L., 1956-1957
    - Gillis, Albert, 1953
    - Gioumousis, George, 1962
    - Gleason, William S., 1962
    - Glick, Richard E., 1959 1961-1962
    - Glockler, George, 1955-1956
    - Godfrey, Fahy, 1957
    - Goldfinger, P., 1962
    - Goldhaber, Maurice, 1962
    - Goose Creek School District, 1959-1960
    - Gray, John K., 1963
    - Granville-Phillips Company, 1958
    - Greek, Bruce F., 1961
    - Green, J.H., 1960-1961
    - Grunwald, Ernest, 1958
  - Correspondence Ha-Hu (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Hackerman, Norman, 1957
    - Hainge, R.F., 1955
    - Hallett, L.T., 1957-1959
    - Hamill, William H., 1962
    - Marker, H.J., 1958
    - Hart, J.L., 1953
    - Hastings, Samuel H., 1956
    - Hatfield, T.N., 1962
    - Hellund, Emil J., 1963
    - Henchman, M.J., 1962
    - Henderson, Watson, 1963
    - Heinglein, A., 1963-1964
    - Herman, Zdenek, 1964
    - Hertzberg, M., 1961
    - Hickam, W.M., 1953
    - Hippie, John A., 1953-1956
    - Hirschfelder, Joseph O., 1958
    - Hoenig, Richard E., 1953 1960
    - Holcomb, H.A., 1960
    - Humble Oil, 1964
    - Humble Recreation Club, 1957
    - Hutchison, Clyde A., 1954-1955
  - Correspondence Ing-Int (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Inghram, Mark G., 1956-1957
    - Institute of Petroleum, 1956
    - Interscience Publishers, Inc., 1955
    - Isbell, A.F., 1960-1961
  - Correspondence Ja-Jo (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Jacoby, Kurt, 1957 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Johnson, G.R.A., 1961 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Johnston, W.H., 1955 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Jolley, H.R., 1953 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Joncich, M.J., 1960 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Journal of Chemical Physics, 1955 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Journal of Physical Chemistry, 1961-1963 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Journal of the American Chemical Society, 1962-1963 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence Ka-Kr (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Kandel, Richard J., 1954 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Kant, F.H., 1956 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Kebarle, Paul, 1961 1964 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Kent, Arthur B., undated (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Kirner, W.R., 1953 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Kiser, Robert W., 1961 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Knox, Lawrence H., 1957 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Krauch, Helmut, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Kraus, John W., 1957 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence La-Lu (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Lampe, Frederick W., 1956-1958 1963-1964
    - Le Goff, P., 1964
    - Libby, W.F., 1960-1963
    - Lindholm, Einar, 1958-1959
    - Linnett, J.W., 1961
    - Lias, Allen R., 1956
    - Liu, David F., 1958
    - London, F., 1953
    - Long, F.A., 1960
    - Lossing, F.P., 1958-1959 1961-1962
    - Lovli, J.W., 1954
    - Lucchesi, P.J., 1963
  - Correspondence Ma-Me (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Maccoll, Allan, 1964
    - McCulloch, T.B., 1956
    - McDowell, C.A., 1953 1956
    - McFadden, W.H., 1960 1962
    - MacGarvey, Charles J., 1963
    - McLafferty, F.W., 1960
    - McMillen, J. Howard, 1956
    - Haddock, J. Kenneth, 1955
    - Magat, M., 1956
    - Magee, Ellington M., 1961
    - Manes, Milton, 1961
    - Mason, H.J., 1953
    - Mathis, J.F., 1961 1963
    - Matsen, F.A., 1963
    - Meier, H.H., 1952
    - Meisels, Gerald G., 1961
    - Melton, Charles E., 1962
    - Meyerson, Seymour, 1963
  - Correspondence Mi-Mu (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Milligan, W.O., 1962
    - Milton, E.A., 1953
    - Mitchell, James T., 1962
    - Mode, V. Allen, 1962
    - Mohler, Fred L., 1954-1956
    - Moore, Walter J., 1956
    - Morgan, L.O., 1960
    - Moritz, Clement, 1959
    - Morrison, J.A., 1963
    - Morrison, J.D., 1957-1958
    - Mulliken, R.S., 1953-1954 1957
    - Murphy, Walter J., 1956
    - Muschlitz, E.E., 1957 1962
  - Correspondence N-O (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Nakajima, Akio, 1960
    - Nance, Billy W., 1960
    - National Science Foundation, 1956 1962
    - Noyes, W. Albert, 1956 1958-1959
    - Ogawa, M., 1961
    - Osberghaus, O., 1964
  - Correspondence P-Re (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Padgett, A.R., 1957
    - Page, F.M., 1962-1964
    - Paulson, J.F., 1961
    - Peterson, E.H., 1963
    - Plesch, P.H., 1955
    - Polymer Corporation Ltd., 1953
    - Pottie, R.F., 1960
    - Price, W.C., 1956
    - Ramsey, Hal H., 1960-1961
    - Rase, Howard F., 1962
    - Redhead, P.A., 1953
    - Reed, R.I., 1962-1963, undated
    - Reese, Kenneth M., 1957
    - Reuben, Bryan G., 1964
  - Correspondence Rh-Ru (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Rhodes, William, 1961-1962
    - Rickard, James A., 1953
    - Ridd, J. H., 1964
    - Roberts, John D., 1960
    - Roberts, Ralph, 1963
    - Roberts, Royston M., 1954
    - Robinson, Charles F., 1956
    - Rogers, Emery H., 1953
    - Rony, Peter R., 1962
    - Rosenstock, Henry H., 1958 1961 1963-1964
    - Ross, Gordon N., 1964
    - Russell, Kenneth, 1964
  - Correspondence Sa-Se (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Saylor, John H., 1956-1957 1959
    - Scheraga, Harold A., 1953 1959-1960 1962
    - Schiller, James C., 1953 1956-1957
    - Schulz, G.J., 1960
    - Science, 1964
    - Scott, John E., Jr., 1963
    - Seyfried, W.D., 1953
  - Correspondence Sh-Sy (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Shriner, Ralph L., 1955
    - Shull, Harrison, 1962
    - Slack, Wayne A., 1964
    - Smith, Noyes D., Jr., 1958
    - Speairs, Mitchell, 1955
    - Spokes, G. Neil, 1961
    - Steiner, Bruce, 1960
    - Stescie, E.W.R., 1960
    - Stevenson, D.P., 1956-1957
    - Stout, J.W., 1960-1963
    - Sugden, T.M., 1962
    - Svec, Harry J., 1958
    - Sydnor, Charles S., 1952
    - Sylvania Electric Products, Inc., 1955
  - Correspondence Ta-V (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Tal'Rose, V.L., 1962
    - Taubert, Rolf, 1960 1963-1964
    - Taylor, Archibald L., Jr., 1952
    - Texas Academy of Science, undated
    - Thomas, L.I., 1963
    - Thomas, W.A., 1953
    - Thyme, John, 1964
    - Tickner, A.W., 1961-1962
    - Tompkins, F.C., 1956 1962
    - Tribble, Robert, 1860
    - Tuffly, B.L., 1958
    - Tunnicliff, Lizabeth G., 1955
    - Turner, Richard B., 1957
    - University of New South Wales, 1962
    - Von Koch, Helge, 1961
  - Correspondence Wa-Wi (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Waddeil, M.T., 1955 1958-1969
    - Wahrhaftig, Austin L., 1963-1964
    - Waldron, J.D., 1958
    - Washburn, H.W., 1956 1959
    - Watanabe, Kenichi, 1954-1955 1960
    - Weissler, G.L., 1959
    - Wentworth, W.E., 1962
    - Westinghouse Electric Corporation, 1955-1956
    - Wexler, Sol, 1959-1962
    - Wiegand, James H., 1954
    - Wilber, Steward A., 1962
    - Wilde, H. Dayton, 1957
    - Winsche, W.E., 1962
    - Wise, Henry, 1963
  - Correspondence Y-Z, no name (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Young, Robert A., 1962
    - Zeitlin, H.R., 1962
    - Zerwekh, Charles, Jr., 1952-1954 1961
    - Zwolinski, Bruno J., 1956
    - no name
- Photographs - Prints and negatives, 4
  Custodial History
  Added to the collection, March 2006.
  - Humble Oil Company, undated (Box 17, Folder 7)
- Frank H. Field papers, Accession 2014:036, 1943-2014; 5; 2.4 Cubic Feet 2 standard record storage boxes
  - FHF papers, 1946-1959, 1 folder (Box 18)
  - FHF papers, 1960-1965, 1 folder (Box 18)
    - [Untitled], 2014.036.003; Still Image (Box SF 1)
  - FHF papers, 1966-1969, 1 folder (Box 18)
  - FHF papers, 1970-1979, 1 folder (Box 18)
  - FHF papers, 1980-1989, 1 folder (Box 18)
  - Church Lecture - Lecture Notes - Fourth Pass - "An Extraordinary Brief Overview of the Origin of Life", 30 July 2000; 1 folder (Box 18)
  - Patent - Chem. Ionization Reminiscence, 1 folder (Box 18)
  - Manuscript- "Chemical Ionization Mass Spectrometry" by Frank H. Field, 1 folder (Box 18)
  - Program - The Joe L. Franklin Memorial Lecture, Rice University - "The Recent Revolution in Mass Spectrometry", November 27, 1984; 1 folder (Box 18)
  - FHF Honor Issue - IJMSIP, 1 folder (Box 18)
  - Correspondence, 1 folder (Box 18)
  - High School, 1 folder (Box 18)
    - High School Excellence in Science Award, 1939; 2014.036.004; Memorabilia (Box SF 1)
  - Chemical Heritage Foundation, 2009-2014; 1 folder (Box 18)
  - Ron MacFarlane - Letter of Assessment, 2007; 1 folder (Box 18)
  - Correspondence, 1989-1996; 1 folder (Box 18)
  - Cas Journal, Vol. 3, No. 3 (Series II), May 1997; 1 journal (Box 18)
  - Cas Journal, Vol. 3, No. 4 (Series II), November 1997; 1 journal (Box 18)
  - Scenes at Retirement Party Rockefeller Univ., March 1, 1989; 2014.036.001; Still Image (Box SF 1)
  - Photographs, 2014.036.002; Still Image (Box SF 1)
  - Biography, 1 folder (Box 18)
  - Presentation Notes, 1 folder (Box 18)
  - FHF Award Lecture at Toronto, 1 folder (Box 18)
  - "Chemical Physics Mass Spectrometry at the Humble Oil and Regining Co.", 1 folder (Box 18)
  - Reprints, 1 folder (Box 18)
  - Remarks for 1996 ASMS Award Talk - Final Version [includes slides], 1 folder (Box 18)
    - [Slides for presentation], 2014.036.005; Still Image (Box SF 1)
  - Awards and Certificates, 1 folder (Box 18)
  - Photograph - Frank H. Field Portrait, 1 folder (Box 18)
    - f56. 6", #1, 2014.036.006; Still Image (Box SF 1)
  - School Papers, 1 folder (Box 18)
  - Patent - Chemical Ionization, 1 file (Box 18)
  - ASMS Lecture Material, May 1996; 1 folder (Box 18)
    - [ASMS Lecture Material], May 1996; 2014.036.007; Still Image (Box SF 1)
  - ASMS New York, May 1980; 1 folder (Box 18)
  - Obituaries, 1 folder (Box 18)
  - FHF Retirement Party - 3/1/89 [Digital Images], 1 folder (Box 18)
    - FHF Retirement Party, March 1, 1989; 2014.036.008; Digital
  - Lecture Rockefeller Univ, 1 folder (Box 18)
  - RU Lecture Slides JPG + RTF, 2014.036.010; Digital (Box SF 1)
  - Powerpoint Slide Show Rockefeller University, 2014.036.009; Digital
  - The Vapor Pressures of Some Organic Fluorides by Frank H. Field, 1944; 1 bound volume (Box 18)
  - Magnetic Studies on Complex Ions of Nickel, Cobalt, and Iron By Frank H. Field, 1947; 1 bound volume (Box 18)
  - Duke University Masters of Arts degree, 1944 (Box 18)
  - Duke University Bachelor of Science Degree, 1943 (Box 18)
  - Duke University Doctor of Philosophy Degree, 1948 (Box 18)
  - Electron Impact Phenomena and the Properties of Gaseous Ions, 1957; 1 Book (Box 19)
  - Electron Impact Phenomena and the Properties of Gaseous Ions Revised Edition, 1970; 1 Book (Box 19)
  - Mass Spectrometry and ion Processes 92 1989, 1 Book (Box 19)
  - Ionization Potentials, Appearance Potentials, and Heats of Formation of Gaseous Positive Ions, 1969; 1 Book (Box 19)
  - Scrapbook, 1989; 1 folder (Box 19)